Learn how sponsored Brands store spotlight format can help you showcase the variety of products
or categories you sell by featuring multiple pages from your brand store within the ad.
This format displays three pages of your store as a visual menu, allowing shoppers to explore what
interests them most while discovering your product range.
Let's explore how to create a store spotlight campaign that features three key areas of your store.
Step 1.
Select sponsored brands and choose the store spotlight format.
Then pick three sub-pages that represent different
product lines or use cases, like new arrivals, bestsellers, or recipes.
For each sub-page, choose
a representative product.
Keeping in mind, images will be pulled from your detail pages
and select a representative label.
Step 2.
Write a unified headline that connects your
featured categories.
For example, essentials for every chef.
Keep it short, clear, and
reflective of your brand's voice.
Step 3.
Use broad keyword themes that capture
diverse shopping interests across your featured pages.
Plus product specific terms tied to
your featured sub-pages.
For product targeting, implement wider category themes to match
the variety of products showcased in your sub-pages, always refining to match your offerings.
Choose from two keyword themes and learn from your search term report to refine your keyword
selection.
Step 4.
Design each featured sub-page for conversion.
Position advertised products
at the top and utilize widgets such as product collections and shoppable images to showcase
your products in action.
Keep branding consistent across the journey to keep shoppers engaged
wherever they click.
This strategy helps to encourage shoppers to discover more of your
store.
Each page preview helps shoppers explore different product lines and find what matches
their needs.
Make informed decisions using your brand store insights to identify opportunities.
Click the Pages tab looking at traffic and conversion rates to help increase traffic on
low-visited pages and capitalize on your top converting pages.
Put learning into practice.
Build a Sponsored Brands Store Spotlight campaign and feature three sections of your brand store.
Watch our other two videos in this series to learn more ways to connect sponsored brands
to your brand store.